F T

MOBILE APP DEVELOPER (ANDROID & FLUTTER)

WWW.LAMINE.ME



ABOUT ME

My Name Is Lamine Fetni I have 4+ years of experience working with native mobile developement especially Android Native and recently the Flutter framework. I've built a variety of apps in domains such as freelance for local businesses and developing for a startup, and personal projects. I also have a rich background in IT and Computer Science subjects including AI / ML



CONTACT

Location:

Bremen, Germany

Mobile:

015140013927

Fmail:

mlaminefetni@gmail.com

Portfolio Website:

Lamine.me

Linkedin: laminefetni



SKILLS

ANDROID/SDK **FLASK**

FLUTTER/DART HTML/CSS/JS

JAVA / KOTLIN MACHINE LEARNING

MYSQL/NOSQL

GIT / FIREBASE

PYTHON

MVVM/MVC/MVP



EXPERIENCES

PROFESSOR ASSISTANT

FACULTÉ NTIC CONSTANTINE 2

2018 - 2019

Due to my good skills in mobile dev while writing my thesis for building a carpooling app, i was picked up as a professor assistant to work on their Flutter mobile client

FULL-TIME FREELANCER

UPWORKS / 1001NIGHTDZ

2019 - 2020

After completing my bachelor degree, I've worked as a freelancer for local businesses (Ex, Restaurants, Clothing

Stores) to build mobile clients for their shops.

ANDROID DEVELOPER

HDARHA STARTUP (H*APP)

2019 - 2020

Worked as the android developer for the startup (Hdarha) using the latest technologies such as Kotlin, Jetpack, MVC, REST-APIs etc.. Sadly the startup was halted due to

the Covid-19 pandemic



EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CONSTANTINE 2

2016 - 2019

COMPUTER SCIENCE BACHELOR DEGREE

University of Constatine 2, Constantine, Algeria Bachelor degree of computer science (3 years)

UNIVERSITY OF

CONSTANTINE 2

2018 - 2019

UNDERGRADUATE THESIS PROGRAM

Development of a mobile application for carpoolin g the elderly, Supervised by Dr. Imene BENSETIRA.

UNIVERSITY OF BREMEN

2020 - PRESENT

DIGITAL MEDIA INFORMATICS MASTER DEGREE

Master's degree in Digital Media, specifically Media

Informatiks, Graduation expected in 2022.



RESEARCH PAPERS

CARPOOLING FOR THE ELDERY

Supervisor: IMENE BENSETIRA Year: 2019

Link: bit.ly/lamine_automation

UBER AND AUTOMATION

Uni-Bremen - Media Theory

Year: 2021

Link: bit.ly/lam_carpooling